hi it's dana here from cwt blows in
store travel group wanting to talk to
you today
about some great medical insurance that
has just been released
from manual life insurance it is
colvid19 pandemic travel plan
and what this insurance is doing is
going to allow consumers to feel
comfortable about wanting to book travel
and knowing that if something happened
and they actually came down with covet
19 and destination
that they are going to be covered for
hospitalization and medical expenses
so it really is a win-win as people are
starting to think about traveling
again so here's what the coverage gives
you it gives you five million dollars
worth of emergency medical non-coveted
related so you fall and break a leg what
have you
everything's going to be covered it
gives you two hundred thousand dollars
worth of coven 19 medical emergency
services
it also allows you to be quarantined and
receive up to 150
per person per day for a 14-day period
if you needed to
self quarantine because of a positive
test in destination
and it also gives you 500 if the travel
advisory from a level 3 changes while in
destination
it allows you to change your flights and
it will cover up to 500
in order to cover your flights to get
you home if you as long as you are not
coved positive so it really is a win-win
it's another piece of mind insurance
that the customer can have
and start to feel confident about
possibly
traveling again in the new year
traveling again in the spring and
wanting to get out of here as the snow
starts to fly
if you look for any information on this
product at all please reach out to us
705-743-8683
or send us an email at info
carlsonwagonly.com
and we will get the information to you
be well have a wonderful weekend